{
    "subject": "resource/Horam",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "England",
    "human_readable": "Horam is from England.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8918864727020264,
            "question": "Is Horam English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.881515383720398,
            "question": "Does Horam have a connection to England?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7114130258560181,
            "question": "Where is Horam from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5977355241775513,
            "question": "Is England the place Horam calls home?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.551021933555603,
            "question": "To which nationality does Horam belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5384575724601746,
            "question": "What country does Horam belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.532677412033081,
            "question": "Where was Horam born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4749740660190582,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Horam's origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3523408770561218,
            "question": "What is Horam's national identity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31509578227996826,
            "question": "What is Horam's citizenship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Horam is from England.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8755_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Horam's national identity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8755_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Horam's origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8755_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Horam born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8755_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8755_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8755_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8755_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8755_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8755_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8755_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8755_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8755_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8755_98.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8755_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's my evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The context mentions that \"Horam is a place in England\" and that it is situated in East Sussex, which confirms that Horam is indeed from England."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Horam is from England.\" Specifically, multiple sources indicate that Horam is located in East Sussex, which is a county in South East England."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}